Oliver Pham

♦ Shakopee, MN, 55379 **▶** pham0428@umn.edu **♦** (763)-313-1329

Overview

I am curious and passionately driven about technology. Teamwork, communication, attention to detail, and fulfillment are important skills that will help me contribute to the success of the company. I acquired many of these skills from college and applied and refined them through my work experience. I look forward to solving challenging problems that will lead to success for the company.

Education

University of Minnesota Twin Cities, B.S. Computer Science

09/2021 - present

Anticipated graduation: Spring 2024

Minneapolis, MN

Relevant Coursework:

- Computing and Programming Concepts, Intro to Algorithms and Data Structures, Machine Architecture and Organization, Advanced Programming Principles, Algorithms and Data

Normandale Community College, Postsecondary Enrollment Options

08/2020 - 05/2021

Relevant Coursework:

Bloomington, MN

- Discrete Structures, Physics 1, Fundamentals of Computers

Skills

Languages (Python, Java, C, C++, HTML, R)

Software (Google Docs, Drive, Sheets, Slides, and Microsoft Word, Excel, and Powerpoint)

Operating Systems (Windows, macOS, Linux/Ubuntu)

Professional Experience

Hy-Vee, Online Personal Shopper

09/2020 - 04/2021

• Engaged with customers and ensuring any special instructions are followed

Shakopee, MN

- Reported customer issues, supply shortages, and inferior products to management immediately
- Collaborated with store departments to ensure efficient service delivery

Marcus Theatres, Theatre Associate

08/2019 - 08/2020

• Responded to guest questions about current facility events and future offerings

- Shakopee, MN
- · Ensured auditoriums, seats, lobby, hallways and restrooms are clean and ready for showtime
- Restocked workstation with supplies and communicated out of stock items to management

Projects

Portfolio Website, oliver7073.github.io/Portfolio □

• Technologies Used: HTML, CSS, and JavaScript

Package Tracker

 Developed an automatic system that can store and fetch the status and information of tracking numbers through AfterShip networking API

Account Generator

- Developed an automatic system that accurately processes and creates several user accounts for a web service
- Designed the automation using Python Selenium module to create the script